He's been fabulous. We'll miss him a lot.
他很出色. 我们会很想念他的.
Will you get a new intern?
你会请一位新的实习生吗?
Yes, but we'll need two new ones to replace Dean.
Yes,但是我们会需要两位新实习生来代替 Dean.
I think we should just hire him when he graduates.
我认为我们应该就雇用他 当他毕业后.
Maybe we will.
或许我们会的.
What's in the box, NuLa?
这个盒子里是什么, NuLa?
A portable CD player.
一个便携式的CD播放器.
Oh, is that what we chipped in for? Great.
Oh, 那就是我们凑份子买的是吗?太好了.
I have something else.
我有别的东西.
What is it?
它是什么?
A soccer ball. From Kevin and me.
一个足球. 来自Kevin和我.
Oh Dean will like that.
Oh Dean会喜欢那个的.
He'll come to his senses some day.
他会醒悟的 某天.
Jarmusch, if I gain one ounce from this cake, I will kill you .
Jarmusch, 如果我长胖1盎司  吃了这个蛋糕后, 我会杀了你.
They're right behind us.
他们就在我们后面.
Kevin. You can't afford to take us to this restaurant.
Kevin. 你负担不起 带我们到这个餐厅.
For a friend like you, Dean?
为了一个你这样朋友, Dean?
Don't think anything of it.
小意思.
Surprise!
没想到吧!